Version 3.14.3:
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.14.2:
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.14.1:
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.14.0:
===============
- Improved usage of network bandwidth for snapshot requests
    Optimized the network bandwidth usage between endpoints and Bloomberg data
    centers for snapshot requests. Customers can request to disable the
    optimization by setting the 'BandwidthSaveModeDisabled' session option.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.13.2:
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.13.1:
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.13.0
===============
- Stability improvements

- Automated network configuration for ZFP over leased lines
	Allow customers that leverage leased lines/routers for Bloomberg
	services (such as existing Bloomberg terminals) to use this infrastructure
	to connect their applications to Zero Foot-Print (ZFP) instances.

	A new utility class, 'ZfpUtil', can be used to
	create a 'SessionOptions' object with the appropriate servers.
	Applications can update the options, including authorization settings,
	but should not change the servers.

	Added a new example, 'ZfpOverLeasedLinesSessionExample'
	to demonstrate how to create a session over ZFP leased lines.

Version 3.12.5
===============
- Added a missing changelog entry for deprecating 'Subscription.SubscriptionStatus' property.

Version 3.12.4
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.12.3
===============
- Consistent range for datetime on self-describing schemas.
	Datetime values outside of the range 1970-01-01 to 2038-01-19 in services
	with a flat schema were interpreted incorrectly. The extended range
	1970-01-01 to 2106-02-07 is now supported.

Version 3.12.2
===============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.12.1
===============
- Improved handling of failure conditions for subscriptions
	Subscriptions are now more resilient to network and infrastructure issues.
	The SDK will now recover internally from failures that previously
	terminated subscriptions.

	The SDK will consider all connections before delivering service
	notifications. 'ServiceDown' will be delivered only when no connection has
	the service available, 'ServiceUp' will be delivered when at least one
	connection has the service. The 'endpoint' field will not be filled in for
	subscription services.

	Delivery of 'SubscriptionStreamsDeactivated' is correctly aligned with the
	instant at which data becomes unavailable, and will be followed by
	'SubscriptionStreamsActivated' once the subscription recovers.

	Applications should use 'SubscriptionStreamsDeactivated' and
	'SubscriptionStreamsActivated' events to identify subscriptions undergoing
	failover.

- The 'Subscription.SubscriptionStatus' property is now deprecated.
	Do not use this property, use the 'Session.GetSubsubscriptionStatus(CorrelationID)' instead.

Version 3.12.0:
===============
- Upgraded .NET Framework target version to 4.5.2.
	The minimum version of the .NET Framework that is supported by Microsoft is
	4.5.2.

- Support for service entity IDs to identify API services

- Setting SessionOptions.Host and SessionOptions.Port no longer resets the list
	of server addresses when more than one address has been provided previously.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.11.4:
===============
- Added new 'encryptionStatus' field to SessionConnectionUp message
	Added new 'encryptionStatus' field to SessionConnectionUp message with possible
	values "Clear", "Verified" and "Encrypted". When the connection is encrypted,
	the new 'encryptionCipher' field will contain the cipher in use in the connection.

- Documentation change
	Clarify the meaning of integer priorities in 'ProviderSession'. Greater values indicate
	higher priorities.

- Added 'SubscriptionStreamsActivated' and 'SubscriptionStreamsDeactivated'
	messages. 'SubscriptionStreamsActivated' is delivered to the application when
	the stream is opened, before data starts ticking for this dataset.
	'SubscriptionStreamsDeactivated' is delivered to the application when an
	opened stream fails. Should be noted that when the stream is recovered
	SubscriptionStreamsActivated will be delivered to the application.

- Removed Code Access Security (CAS) support.
	Microsoft updated their security guidelines to state that CAS should not be
	used.
	https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/standard/security/secure-coding-guidelines

- Stability improvements

Version 3.11.3:
===============
- Added support for 'authId', replacing 'emrsId', in 'AuthorizationRequests'
	Added support for using the more general 'authId' field as a replacement
	for the 'emrsId' field in 'AuthorizationRequest' messages (//blp/apiauth
	service).  The SDK will now translate 'emrsId' into 'authId' internally
	when only the former is present in the message.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.11.2:
===============
- Added support for generation of tokens with user provided userId and IP
	When using 'AuthorizationMode=USER_AND_APPLICATION' in 'SessionOptions',
	the application can now use 'AuthorizationType=MANUAL' to provide the user
	id and IP address.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.11.1:
===============
- Always return fully qualified strings when iterating over subscriptions
	'Subscription.subscriptionString' will always return fully qualified topic
	strings when iterating over subscriptions using a 'SubscriptionIterator'.
	If it is called on a user-created 'Subscription' object, it will return
	the original string provided by the user.

- 'minOccurs' defaults to 0 for SEQUENCE elements
	When parsing a schema, the 'minOccurs' value for 'SEQUENCE' elements will
	now default to 0. This fix allows empty arrays in messages to be compliant
	with their schema.

- Provide error information in RequestFailure messages for snapshot requests
	When a RequestTemplate is terminated due to an error, the error
	information will also appear in RequestFailure messages for any
	outstanding snapshot requests using that template.

- SnapshotRequestTemplateExample binary is included in SDK package

- Stability improvements

Version 3.11.0:
===============
- Support for SSL (TLS) connections
	The SDK now supports secure connections using public-key based connection
	authentication. A new class 'TlsOptions' is provided which allows the user
	to specify secure credentials. The TlsOptions can be added to
	'SessionOptions' for use during connection establishment.
- Stability improvements

Version 3.10.3:
===============
- RoutingDomainManager component logic changes
	AddEndpoint now handles all cases when endpoint was and was not connected
	before, known and not known to belong to a cluster. GetRoutingCandidates
	now include endpoints removed from clusters and correctly preventing
	cases with duplicates in priority map. Unit tests were ported from C++
	version.
- Stability improvements

Version 3.10.2:
===============
- Publisher topic lifetime changes
	Changed topic lifetime semantics. Calling 'deleteTopic*' on a subscribed
	topic no longer delivers 'TopicUnsubscribed' to the application as this
	caused an inconsistency between the state in the application and the
	platform.  A subscribed topic that is deleted is now in the same state that
	a topic that was subscribed and never created.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.10.1:
===============
- Service open timeouts configurable via SessionOptions
	The SDK supports configurable timeouts for requests sent when a service is
	opened. Clients can use 'SessionOptions.ServiceCheckTimeout' to configure
	the timeout for identifying the version informationf for the service
	schema, and 'SessionOptions.ServiceDownloadTimeout' to configure the
	timeout for downloading the service schema.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.10.0:
===============
- Expose recap metadata in 'Blpapi.Message'
	Some subscription data messages represent not real-time data, but rather
	"context" for future ticks; these messages are delivered to subscribers as
	needed (eg. when subscriptions are started, or when the infrastructure
	detects a gap in the tick stream) and thus might not be delivered at the
	same point in the tick stream for two independent subscribers to the same
	data. These *recap* messages (aka "initial paints") have previously been
	identified only in service-specific ways--e.g. recaps for the
	'//blp/mktdata' service contain a 'MKTDATA_EVENT_TYPE' field set to
	'SUMMARY'. There is now an additional interface for examining the recap
	type of a subscription data message directly: the RecapType of Message.

- Snapshot requests for subscription services
	The SDK supports receiving up-to-date data on an on-demand basis
	from subscription services using a new type of request known as a
	snapshot request. This type of request enables the receipt of
	up-to-date data with significantly lower latency compared to
	starting a new subscription each time. In addition, it helps to
	avoid the overhead of the alternate approach which is to maintain
	a long-running subscription used to update a local cache.
	The data is obtained using a request-response style interaction.
	The snapshot is first set up using the new method
	'Session::createSnapshotRequestTemplate' which returns a request
	template handle represented by the new 'RequestTemplate' class.
	Whenever a subscription data snapshot is required, the
	request template can be sent using 'Session::sendRequest' and the
	corresponding data is received in a regular response. New admin
	events 'RequestTemplateAvailable', 'RequestTemplatePending',
	'RequestTemplateTerminated' provide feedback on changes to the
	state of an active request template.


- Stability improvements

Version 3.9.4:
==============
- Fixes an issue causing a failure to decode some ticks

- Stability improvements

Version 3.9.3:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.9.2:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.9.1:
==============
- Session startup waits for multiple connections to be established

- Stability improvements

Version 3.9.0:
==============
- Horizontal scaling support for multi-stream
	The SDK may potentially connect to more than one Point of Presence (POPs)
	in one or more cluster backends to receive data from multiple streams
	simultaneously for a single subscribed topic. Rebalance request from the
	backend will also be handled by moving existing data streams to new POPs in
	the same or different clusters.
- Multi-cluster support in .NET SDK
	The SDK may use multiple clusters of Points of Presence, and will attempt
	to route preferentially based on the order of appearance, in the session
	options, of the first Point of Presence in a given cluster.

Version 3.8.7:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.6:
==============
- Improved behavior when authorizing multi-connection sessions
	For sessions with multiple connections, a single authorization
	request will now consistently authorize all connections. (In
	prior releases, some authorization modes would require
	multiple authorizations for multiple connections.) To support
	legacy applications that may send multiple (now redundant)
	authorization requests, when authorization succeeds, all the
	redundant authorization requests submitted for the same
	identity will also receive an authorization success
	message. That identity will remain authorized until the
	authorization is revoked, or the client code cancels all
	authorization requests submitted for that identity. An
	identity that gets deauthorized due to failed authorization,
	authorization revocation, or cancellation of all prior
	authorization requests can be reauthorized by sending new
	authorization requests.

- Updated DDM version needed for token based authorization
	Token-based authorization using DDM (aka "Platform") versions
	prior to 3.16.0.0 is no longer supported.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.5:
==============
- Deprecate 'NameEnumerationTable'
	Classes 'NameEnumeration' and 'NameEnumerationTable' are now deprecated
	and the example 'NameEnumerationExample', which exhibited use of these
	classes, has been removed accordingly.  Instances of
	'NameEnumerationTable' are enumeration-like objects constructed, through
	reflection, from classes implementing the 'NameEnumeration' marker
	interface.  Clients should use 'System.Enum' instead.

- Provide connection information in 'ServiceDown' and 'ServiceUp' messages
	'ServiceDown' and 'ServiceUp' messages include an 'endpoint' field that
	contains the hostname and port number of the relevant connection.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.4:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.3:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.2:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.1:
==============
- Record receipt time for messages
	The SDK now provides an interface, 'Message.TimeReceived', for
	interrogating the time at which a message was received and processed by
	the library. This provides the facility for clients to measure the amount
	of time each message spends in the client event queue, by comparing the
	time the message was received by the library with the time, as reported by
	'DateTime.UtcNow', at which it is extracted from the client event
	queue. For performance reasons, receipt times are *not* recorded for
	subscription data messages by default; clients can use the
	'SessionOptions.RecordSubscriptionDataReceiveTimes' setting to request
	receipt times for all messages.

- Send host identification information during session establishment
	In order to support usage auditing, BLPAPI will report the host name and
	IP address (non-NAT) used for establishing the session with the Bloomberg
	infrastructure.

- Replace treasury bill CUSIP with that of a bill expiring in 2044
	SimpleSubscriptionExample and SimpleRefDataExample contain a CUSIP for a
	treasury bill; this CUSIP has been changed to one corresponding to a
	treasury bill that will not expire for 30 years.

- Extended version identifier interfaces
	The new 'VersionInfo.versionIdentifier' interface provides more
	fine-grained release tracking information for Bloomberg support.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.8.0:
==============
- Service-level failover
	When a session has multiple connections and a service becomes unavailable
	on one connection (and a 'ServiceDown' message is added to the event
	queue) outstanding requests and subscriptions for that service (only) will
	now be automatically migrated to a connection where the service is
	available (and a 'ServiceUp' message will be added to the event queue), if
	such a connection exists. Note that this can result in a single session
	using multiple connections simultaneously for different services.

- Additional information in 'ServiceUp' and 'ServiceDown' messages
	The 'ServiceUp' and 'ServiceDown' messages have been extended with
	detailed information about which parts of the service have become
	(un)available.

- Include all local and remote display IP addresses in generateToken request
	BLPAPI will report all detected local IP addresses as well as any
	remote display IP addresses (Citrix or RDP) in the token
	generation request. This extends the remote IP address support to
	enable more flexible permissioning schemes, but it requires an
	updated token service that can process the additional information.

- Cancel subscriptions and requests on revoked authorization
	When the authorization for an identity is revoked (e g. due to an
	authorization change or, for BPS authorization, a login at a different
	location) or cancelled by the application, all subscriptions and pending
	requests using that identity are now terminated (for active subscriptions)
	or failed (for pending requests and pending subscriptions).

- Authorization token uses display IP address when a remote display is in use
	When a blpapi application is being executed in a Citrix
	(XenApp/XenDesktop) environment, the 'Session::generateToken'
	function now uses the "display IP address" to identify where the
	application is running, instead of using the physical IP address
	as reported by the operating system. This enables applications
	using BPS permissioning to be run remotely (even in virtual
	environments) as long as they are using the same display as a
	Bloomberg terminal. This feature supports only a single level of
	remoting: if an application is running on machine A which has a
	remote display on machine B and machine B has a remote display on
	machine C, 'Session::generateToken' will generate a token for
	authorization on machine B.

- Addition of testing interface for logging system
	A 'Logging.LogTestMessage' function has been added to allow clients
	to test the library's logging configuration.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.7.2:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.7.1:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.7.0:
==============
- Support service deregistration
	ProviderSession supports service deregistration. If service is registered,
	it sends deregistration request, deletes all topics and removes all
	subscriptions and pending requests in the service, and generates a
	ServiceStatus event containing a ServiceDeregistered message. If service
	registration is pending, it cancels the registration, sends deregistration
	request if registration request is already sent out, and generates a
	ServiceStatus event containing a ServiceRegisterFailure message. If the
	service is not registered nor pending, it returns an error.

- Fine-grained service registration
	Support is provided for separate registration of the publication,
	operations (request-response), and resolution components of a service.
	This provides to ability to, for example, write a publisher and its
	corresponding resolver as entirely separate applications running in
	different processes (and different machines). See
	'ServiceRegistrationOptions.PartsToRegister' for further details.

- Add sub-service code support
	Publishers can now collaborate with resolvers to route subscription
	requests based on "sub-service codes", which are integer identifiers
	between 0 and 2**24. Publishers can advertise the set of sub-service
	codes they support (and their priority relative to other publishers for
	each sub-service code) either at the time the service is registered
	(via 'ServiceRegistrationOptions.AddSubServiceCodeRange') or
	dynamically over the lifetime of the publisher (via
	'ProviderSession.ActivateSubServiceCodeRange' and
	'ProviderSession.DeactivateSubServiceCodeRange'). In responding to a
	resolution request, a resolver can set the 'subServiceCode' element of
	the 'PermissionResponse', and the subscription request will be routed
	only to a publisher that has advertised that particular sub-service
	code.

- Support pub-sub contribution services
	This SDK supports contribution services that have been configured to use the
	publication protocol for each contributed tick. Existing services (that
	use the request-response protocol for contributed ticks) are unaffected.

- Report errors when attempting to publish the same field multiple times
	The documentation for 'EventFormatter' has always specified undefined
	behavior if clients attempt to set the same field in a tick multiple
	times. Previous versions of the library would silently allow such usage
	(with unspecified semantics for which value would be published).
	'EventFormatter' will now detect and report most instances of this type
	of misuse.

- Topic strings can be marked as not requiring resolution
	Clients with access to fully-resolved topic strings can now use the
	'SubscriptionList.AddResolved' family of functions to advise the
	Bloomberg infrastructure that such topics do not require resolution. It
	is at the discretion of the infrastructure whether or not such advice
	actually allows avoidance of the resolution phase of subscription.

- New session option to disable keep-alive mechanism
	Clients can now use the 'SessionOptions.SetKeepAliveEnabled' function
	to disable or enable a session's keep-alive mechanism.  In addition,
	the 'SessionOptions.KeepAliveEnabled' function can be used to query
	the enabled state of the keep-alive mechanism.

- Drop support for V2 platform
	The SDK no longer supports publishing to Platform versions before 3.0.0.

- Providers can delete topics
	The new 'ProviderSession.DeleteTopic*' interfaces allow publishers to
	free the resources associated with topics created using
	'ProviderSession.CreateTopic*'. See 'Providersession' for details.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.6.3:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.6.2:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.6.1:
==============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.6.0:
==============
- Publishers can clear internal cached values
	This version adds support to allow publishers to publish null values
	by calling 'EventFormatter.setElementNull'. Publishing null clears any
	value for that field currently cached by the data distribution platform.

- Demonstrate a valid behavior on DataLoss
	Sample implementation of application processing DataLoss message added to
	SubscriptionWithEventHandlerExample. Note that this behavior may not be the
	most appropriate behavior for your application.

- SecurityLookupExample added
	New example has been added to demonstrate the use of Ticker Lookup
	service, //blp/instruments.

- Resubscribe with resubscription ID
	One more method in Session is provided to support resubscription with
	a user-specified resubscription ID. This resubscription ID appears in
	the subscription status messages('SubscriptionStarted' and
	'SubscriptionFailure') associated with this resubscription request,
	differentiating them from status messages for other resubsubscriptions
	and from status messages from the initial subscription.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.5.1:
=============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.5.0:
=============
- Deliver DataLoss when library drops events
	The library drops events when the number of events outstanding for
	delivery exceeds the specified threshold controlled by SessionOptions
	maxEventQueueSize.

	A new ADMIN message of type DataLoss will be delivered to notify the
	client about lost data. The correlationID property attached to the
	DataLoss message identifies the affected subscription.

- High-precision time
	The Datetime type has been extended with support for receiving
	high-precision fractional seconds, with accessors for the
	fraction-of-second as milliseconds, microseconds, nanoseconds, and
	picoseconds, with these accessors ignoring/truncating higher-resolution
	parts as necessary.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.8:
=============
- Performance improvement in default configuration
	For performance improvement, the default value of SessionOption property
	maxEventQueueSize has been changed from 512 to 10000.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.7:
=============
- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.6:
=============
- Support fragmented messages
	Users can check Message.FragmentType property to determine if message is
	a fragment of a larger message. Most messages won't be fragmented so the
	above property will read Message.Fragment.NONE. Consuming application
	should be prepared to receive a Message.Fragment.START before receiving
	Message.Fragment.END in which case previously received message fragments
	(start and any intermediate fragments) should be discarded.

- Per-connection authorization implemented inside the library
	Applications are no longer required to send an authorization request
	per each backend they intend to use. This functionality is now provided
	by the library.

- Introduce new dead peer detection mechanism
	The new functionality is controlled by two parameters: inactivity time
	and response timeout. Inactivity time controls the amount of time
	without any read activity on the connection before the library will ping
	the peer. The peer will be declared "dead" if ping response (or other
	data) is not received within response timeout interval after the ping.
	The behaviour can be controlled using following SessionOption
	properties:
	        DefaultKeepAliveInactivityTime
	        DefaultKeepAliveResponseTimeout
	This feature is only available if connected to a compatible server.

- Clarify requirements for starting Sessions with external dispatcher
	Attempts to start a Session/ProviderSession configured with an external
	dispatcher will now fail unless the provided EventDispatcher object has
	already been started. This change is expected to help users who had
	inadvertently created sessions with a non-started EventDispatcher;
	sessions created this way would not emit any events.

- PagePublisherExample enhanced to handle permission request
	PagePublisherExample now demonstrates basic handling of permission request.

- ContributionsPageExample can publish on user specified topic
	In ContributionsPageExample, users can specify the topic to publish
	using the "-t" option at command line.

- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.5:
=============
- Support multiple simultaneous active connections to backend servers
	ProviderSession.registerService request will announce published services
	through all conencted backends. A new SERVICE_STATUS message was
	introduced: ServiceAvailabilityInfo to inform the publishing application
	about the current list of backends that carry their service.

	Applications will be required to send an authorization request per
	each backend they intend to use (it's recommended to send as many as
	the number of configured backends)

- Support publishing request/response services
	Publishing applications can now register to publish interactive
	services: requests from clients will be routed to such publishers, who
	would create a response with Service.createResponseEvent() and send it
	back with ProviderSession.sendResponse(). Included
	RequestServiceExample demonstrates an implementation of both client and
	server applications.

- Support user-provided sequence numbers
	The presence of sequence numbers in published events will enable a
	seamless (data loss free) failover in case of a publisher loss.

	EventFormatter was extended with new overloads for appendMessage() and
	appendRecapMessage() which take a sequence number as one of the arguments
	where added to allow publishers insert sequence numbers into message they
	publish.

- Topic-level permissioning
	Publishers can report the list of EIDs and the permissioning service
	information per Topic in PermissionResponse (in a response to
	PermissionRequest sent by Platform on behalf of a subscriber). The
	Platform will continuously monitor entitlements of that subscriber to
	ensure eligibility to receive the data on the Topic.  In case the
	permissions of the subscriber make him ineligible, the Platform will
	terminate that subscription.

- Change the names of the methods in Bloomberglp.Blpapi.Logging
	The following methods have been renamed:
	    Callback.onMessage -> Callback.OnMessage
	    registerCallback -> RegisterCallback
	    deRegisterCallback -> DeregisterCallback

- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.3:
=============
- Connection timeout configurable via SessionOptions
	The default connection timout changed to be 5 sec. Users can change
	that value using SessionOptions::setConnectTimeout().

- Expose more EMRS information to users
	Added userName, appName, serviceName and deviceAddress to permission
	request.

- Datetime can now be used as a Dictionary key

- Stability improvements

Version 3.4.2:
==============
- Stability release
	Bloomberglp.Blpapi.dll assembly is now marked with
	System.Security.AllowPartiallyTrustedCallers attribute, as such it can
	now be used by partially trusted callers.

Version 3.4.1:
==============
- Differentiate log messages based on session id in the log file
	When a single process has more than one active session, log messages coming
	from different sessions are tagged with the session id.

- Topic.IsValid() has been removed
	When a topic does not exist we return null instead of an empty invalid
	Topic object.

- Support concurrent openService & registerService operations
	Multiple ProviderSession.OpenService() & ProviderSession.RegisterService()
	operations can run concurrently. Either if started explicitly or
	implicitly via ProviderSession.resolve(), ProviderSession.createTopics(),
	and Session.subscribe() calls.

- Connection timeout consist with C++ implementation
	Session TCP connect will timeout after 2 seconds in case destination host
	is unreachable (as in other SDKs).

Version 3.4.0:
==============
- All new ProviderSession, independent from Sesssion:
	Initial publishing implementation offered ProviderSession which was a
	subclass of Session. Thus it was possible to do subscriptions on
	ProviderSession. It's no longer the case: ProviderSession and Session
	are no longer related; new classes provide a true "writer" and "reader"
	interfaces respectively. New session classes share a common base -
	AbstractSession, which defines interfaces for session control, and
	user authorization.

- Multiple publisher support:
	Multiple publishers for the same feed/topic are now supported, providing
	redundancy/fan-in services.
	- Publisher group ID: When registering a service you now can specify
	  a group ID. If not specified, each provider session will have a
	  unique group ID (default behavior). The group ID is used for
	  clustering together a set of service publishers.
	  The group ID controls the behavior of the multiple publishers. Using
	  the same group ID for a set of publishers you can provide redundancy
	  between the publishers. Using a different group IDs users can
	  implement publisher fan-in (for the same or different topics).

	- Redundancy: When publishers are registered with the same group ID, the
	  platform will manage the list of publishers and will activate the
	  feed from only one of them at any given time.
	  In order to support this feature two new TOPIC_STATUS messages exist:
	  TopicActivated & TopicDeactivated.
	  A publisher should start publishing on a given topic only after a
	  TopicActivated message has been received. When a publisher receives
	  the TopicDeactivated notification message, it should stop publishing
	  on the topic.
	  All information that is streamed from a publisher before it received
	  the TopicActivated message, or after it received the
	  TopicDeactivated message will be discarded by the platform.
	  Publishers on the same group are required to publish identical tick
	  streams.

	- Topic fan-in: Information from different group IDs publishers will be
	  combined in to one stream towards the subscribers. It's up to the
	  publishers to make sure that different group IDs will not publish
	  redundant information.
	  Setting the group ID:
	  ...
	  ServiceRegistrationOptions options = new ServiceRegistrationOptions();
	  options.GroupId = "SomeGroupID";
	  providerSession.RegisterService(serviceName, identity, options);
	  ...

- Failover support for both publisher- and subscriber-type clients
	A session can be provided with a list of platform servers. Depending
	on the session configuration, if the platform server goes down the
	session will try to reconnect to the next platform server in the list.
	By default, the auto restart option is disabled, to enable it do:
	...
	SessionOptions options = new SessionOptions();
	options.AutoRestartOnDisconnection = true;
	ProviderSession session = new ProviderSession(options, myEventHandler);
	...

	Users should expect that sometimes (the worst case scenario) the
	library might not be able to failover some published services or topics
	to the backup system and will notify the user with
	ServiceFailoverError and TopicFailoverError messages as appropriate.

- Topic creation/resolution:
	The API ProviderSession.CreateTopic() has been deprecated.

	Topic resolution and management has moved from the library to the
	platform server, thus each time the library is trying to resolve or
	create a topic, a message is sent to the platform. In order to save in
	bandwidth and response time the new API supports creation of multiple
	topics in a single call.

	Once a topic has been created it is cached by the library (in the
	process memory). In order to get a reference to a cached instance
	using a message object, the API ProviderSession.GetTopic() was introduced.

	In order to maintain backward compatibility, the deprecated API
	ProviderSession.CreateTopic() can still be used, but it assumes that the
	topic object was previously resolved & created using either
	ProviderSession.CreateTopics() API. In "compat33x" mode it's sufficient to
	call ProviderSession.Resolve[Async]() which does both resolving and topic
	creation with the platform. As a result, the ProviderSession.CreateTopic()
	API is now a local call (i.e. the library does not interact with the
	platform).

	When creating a topic using either ProviderSession.CreateTopics() API or
	ProviderSession.Resolve()/CreateTopics() API, the library generates the
	following events to the client in case of a successful operation:
	- RESOLUTION_STATUS event with ResolutionSuccess message
	- TOPIC_STATUS event with TopicCreated and TopicActivated (or
	  TopicDeactivated, if the provider was not elected primary for the
	  group) messages.

- Topic recap:
	A topic recap message, is a message generated by the client
	application and should include ALL the current information for the
	topic (the platform cache will get reset to whatever values came in
	the recap message, empty fields will clear cache values; that's
	different from a regular tick where absent field values mean "no
	change"). There are two logical types of a topic recap message:

	- Solicited topic recap message: The platform server can decide that
	  the information it has stored in cache is not valid anymore, in that
	  case the publisher will receive a TOPIC_STATUS event with TopicRecap
	  message. The message will include a correlation ID that should be
	  incorporated into the Topic recap response.
	...
	Topic topic = providerSession.GetTopic(msg);
	CorrelationID cid = msg.CorrelationID;
	Event event = service.CreatePublishEvent();
	EventFormatter eventFormatter = new EventFormatter(event);
	eventFormatter.AppendRecapMessage(topic, cid);
	...

	- Unsolicited topic recap message:
	  The client application can decide on its own (based on its own internal
	  logic) to send a recap message to the platform.  Sending a topic
	  recap message is done the same way as sending a regular update
	  message, with two changes: When appending a message to the event,
	  you should use the EventFormatter.AppendRecapMessage() API (vs the
	  EventFormatter.AppendMessage()) and, all fields of the topic recap
	  message should be filled. The code fragment below demonstrates
	  sending a recap message:
	...
	Event event = service.CreatePublishEvent();
	EventFormatter eventFormatter = new EventFormatter(event);
	eventFormatter.AppendRecapMessage(topic, null);
	...

- Initial paint events:
	Publishing applications implementing "initial paint" functionality
	must do that by sending a recap message as described above; formatting
	these events with EventFormatter.AppendMessage() is not supported. The
	recap will be requested by the platform if the service's metadata
	specifies that publishers supports recaps (see discussion on solicited
	topic recap messages above). Otherwise publishers can provide the
	"initial paint" by sending an unsolicited recap of the topic in
	response to TopicActivated notification.

- Dynamically updating entitlements in Identity
	Authorization request no longer completes when Identity is authorized,
	AuthorizationSuccess message will arrive in a PARTIAL_RESPONSE event.
	The authorization request will remain outstanding delivering
	entitlements updates.

- Support BBCOMM auto start on 64-bit OS
	BBCOMM will be autostarted in DAPI mode from .NET applications running in
	64-bit process on Windows platform with assistance of native 64-bit library
	blpdapisup_64.dll.

- Identity extended to include user's "seat" type
	An authorized Identity object can detail whether the authenticated user is
	a BLP Professional Service user or not.

- PermissionRequest extended to support non-user subscribers
	PermissionRequest message have been extended to supply "seat" type
	information of the subscriber and an application ID (if subscriber used
	application authentication).

- Support custom loggers
	BLPAPI now supports logging through customer-provided logging callback.

- Connection up/down notifications
	Added two new message types to SessionStatus event type:
	SessionConnectionUp and SessionConnectionDown. This way the lifetime
	of the connection to the backend server and the lifetime of the
	session can be reported independently as connections to backend can
	drop/recover without having the library terminate the session.
